(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
T-O-W-A、トワ！
T-O-W-A, Towa!
T-O-W-A、go！
T-O-W-A, go!
Break your xxx 応援セット
Break your xxx Support Set
受注販売グッズ①
Pre-order Goods 1
受注販売グッズ②
Pre-order Goods 2
Made-to-order items ②
受注販売グッズ③
Made-to-order items ③
ライブグッズ2次販売開始！
2nd round of live goods sales started!
風を吹くように　散ってしまった花の色を
Like the wind blowing, the color of the flowers that have scattered,
あなたが知ることはきっと無いのでしょう
you will surely never know.
推しの曲、めっちゃいいね！
My fave's song is so good!
みるハコ チャーンス！
Miruhako Chance!
みるハコなら臨場感たっぷりで推しのコンテンツが楽しめる！
With Miruhako, you can enjoy your fave's content with a great sense of presence!
みるハコ最高！
Miruhako is the best!
推し活増やそう、みるハコ！
Let's do more fan activities, Miruhako!
JOYSOUND
Break your xxx 応援セット
Break your xxx Support Set
グッズ販売期間 2023.9.28 21:00 - 10.23 18:00
Goods Sale Period: Sep 28, 2023, 21:00 - Oct 23, 18:00
受注販売グッズ①
Made-to-order Goods 1
受注販売グッズ②
Made-to-order Goods 2
受注販売グッズ③
Made-to-order Goods 3
Break your xxx グッズ
Break your xxx Goods
hololive production OFFICIAL SHOP / Geek Jack にてライブグッズ2次販売開始！
Live goods 2nd round sales started at hololive production OFFICIAL SHOP / Geek Jack!
#常闇トワ1stソロライブ
#TokoyamiTowa1stSoloLive
Tokoyami Towa 1st solo live "Break your xxx"
Break your xxx 応援セット ¥10,500
Break your xxx Support Set - ¥10,500
Break your xxx 受注販売グッズ①
Break your xxx Made-to-order Goods (1)
Break your xxx 受注販売グッズ②
Break your xxx Made-to-order Goods (2)
Break your xxx 受注販売グッズ③
Break your xxx Made-to-order Goods (3)
推しの曲、めっちゃいいね。
My fave's song is so good!
みるハコ、チャンス！
Miruhako, Chance!
みるハコなら臨場感たっぷりで推しのコンテンツが楽しめる。
With Miruhako, you can enjoy your fave's content
with an immersive experience.
みるハコ最高！
Miruhako is the best!
音も増やそう。
Let's turn up the sound!
みるハコ by JOYSOUND
Miruhako by JOYSOUND
Break your xxx 応援セット
Break your xxx Support Set
受注販売グッズ①
Made-to-Order Merchandise ①
Attention
カメラ・ビデオ撮影禁止 / フラッシュ撮影禁止 / 係員の指示に従ってください
No recording or filming / No flash photography / Please follow staff instructions
あー、こんやっぷー、トワ様です！
Ah, Kon-yappu! It's Towa-sama!
イェーイ！みんな見えてるよ！
Yay! I can see everyone!
えー、緊張してます。はい。
Um, I'm nervous. Yes.
はい、ということで！もうそろそろ...
Alright, then! Very soon...
常闇トワ 1stソロライブ "Break your ×××"、始まるぞー！
Tokoyami Towa's 1st Solo Live, "Break your ×××", is starting!
うふふふふ。声がすごいじゃん。
Hehehe. Your voices are amazing.
一緒に盛り上がる準備はできてるかー！？
Are you ready to have a blast together!?
声出す準備も、できてるかー！？
Are you ready to shout your hearts out too!?
いくぞー！
Here we go!
聞かせて
Let me hear it
みんなー！今日は常闇トワ 1st ソロライブに来てくれてありがとう！
Everyone! Thank you for coming to Tokoyami Towa's 1st Solo Live today!
最後まで盛り上がっていくぞー！
Let's keep this energy up until the very end!
爪を磨いたなら　まだ子供のようなあなたの為に
Once I've polished my nails, for you who are still like a child
あぁ　試したいのなら　そう愚かな手に手錠をかけて
Ah, if you want to test me, then put handcuffs on those foolish hands
常世の闇に囚われたまま　甘い眩暈が胸を噛んでて
Still trapped in the darkness of the underworld, a sweet dizziness gnaws at my chest
幾つもの後悔を　捧げて
Offering up countless regrets
さりげない合図に隠れた　答えはすぐに分からせてあげる
The answer hidden in a casual sign, I'll let you know right away
微睡に塗れた　拒んだままに　受け止めてあげる
Drowned in a daze, I will accept you just as you are, refusing me
ほら　悲鳴を聞かせて
Now, let me hear your scream
じゃあ　指を鳴らしたなら　こねこねこのような私の為に
Then, if I snap my fingers, for me who's like a kitten
あぁ　喉が渇いたわ　薄紅の口に指を散らして
Ah, my throat is parched, scattering fingers on my light crimson lips
狭い牢屋に閉じ込めたまま　首輪に繋がれたいの
Still locked in a narrow cage, I want to be tethered by a collar
下らないルールじゃ奪えない　自由は既にこの手の中に有る
Foolish rules cannot take it away, freedom is already in these hands
愛情では測れない　狂ったままに選ばせてあげる
It cannot be measured by love, I will let you choose in your madness
ほら　ここを灼いて
Now, sear this place
分からないふりをして　寝惚けてるの？
Are you pretending not to know, half-asleep?
もっと熱い暗闇を見せて　ねぇ
Show me an even hotter darkness, hey
さりげない合図に隠れた　答えはすぐに分からせてあげる
The answer hidden in a casual sign, I'll let you know right away
微睡に塗れた　拒んだままに　受け止めてあげる
Drowned in a daze, I will accept you just as you are, refusing me
常闇に響き　刻むこの魔法　分からせてあげる
Resonating in eternal darkness, this carving magic, I'll let you know
ほら　悲鳴を聞かせてよ
Now, let me hear your scream
夢見ないで　ほら聞かせて
Don't dream, now let me hear it
トワ様ー！
Towa-sama!
来たぞー！
I'm here!
やべー、めっちゃ緊張してる。
Oh man, I'm so nervous.
やべー、はぁー...すごい...
Oh man, phew... Amazing...
みんなが目の前にいますよー！
Everyone is right in front of me!
いぇーい！見えてるー？みんなー！
Yay! Can you see me? Everyone!
やばい、緊張伝わった？
Oh no, did my nervousness come across?
あははは、やめて。
Ahahaha, stop it.
はい、ということで、こんやっぴー、ホロライブ...
All right, well then, Kon-yappi, Hololive...
お疲れ様ですー！
Good job, everyone!
ちょっと一旦お水飲もう、口パサパサなのよ。
I'm going to drink some water, my mouth is dry.
お水美味しい、肝すぎー。
The water is delicious, it's too good!
ふぅ、じゃないよ、ふぅじゃ。
Don't 'Phew' me!
はい、ということでみなさん、なんとソロライブに来ました。
All right, everyone, I've finally made it to my solo live.
えー、今日みんなグッズ買ってくれた？
Um, did everyone buy the merch today?
わぁ、本当だ、すげー。
Wow, you really did! Awesome.
Tシャツほら、なんとお揃いコーデみたいになってる。
Look, the T-shirts make us look like we're in matching outfits.
いいね、すごい。で、今ここでね、喋りながらね緊張ほぐしてるっていう。
Nice, really nice. And right now, I'm loosening up my nerves as I talk.
ふぅ、もうすごい、緊張したよ、もうこれ。
Phew, I was so nervous about this.
え？
Huh?
まあまあまあ、いいんですよそんなのは。はい。
Well, well, that's fine. Anyway...
ということで、今日はね、ライブのタオルとかもね、
So, today, while holding your concert towels...
こうちょっとこう持ちながらみんなでこうイエーイとかってやっていきたいなとか思ってるので、ぜひ首とかにかけて待っててください。
I want us all to go 'Yeah!' together, so please wear them around your necks and wait.
はい、そしてね、なんとスタンディングということで、みんな足大丈夫？
And since it's a standing concert, are your legs okay, everyone?
おー、もう元気そうだよね。
Oh, you guys look energetic.
トワのほら、も、こんなだよ今。
Look at Towa, I'm like this right now.
いいね、この笑い声が聞こえてくるのとかもすごい、いい。ありがとう。
I love how I can hear your laughter. It's great. Thank you.
はい、でね、そうスタンディングなので、
Right, since it's standing room...
周りにね、気をつけながらね、
be careful of those around you,
ぜひ最後まで一緒に盛り上がっていけたらなと思います。
and let's have a great time together until the end!
そして、なんと今日はね、現地の人だけじゃございません！
And today, it's not just the people here at the venue!
インターネットから応援してくれてるみんなもいます！
There are also people supporting us from the internet!
インターネットから見てるみんな、ヤッホー、お疲れ様だよー。
Everyone watching online, hello! Thanks for tuning in!
はい、コメントも見えてますよ。ありがとうございます。
Yes, I can see your comments too. Thank you very much.
でね、なんとこのあともね、たくさん歌う予定なんですけれども、
I'm planning to sing a lot more after this, but...
あと2曲ほど歌ったら、YouTubeとツイッチのね、今ちょっとあのチラ見せっていうのやってるんですけれども、そちらが終わってしまいます。
after about two more songs, the sneak peek on YouTube and Twitch will end.
ええー
Eee!
共鳴するのやめてくれない？
Could you stop echoing like that?
はい、興味がある方はね、チケットをぜひ買って頂けたらなと思います。
If you're interested, I hope you'll buy a ticket.
概要欄に書いてあるので、チェックチェックしてみてね。
The details are in the description, so please check it out.
準備できてますか？
Are you ready?
準備、もっとできてる人、大きい声もっと出してください。
If you're ready, let me hear you louder!
できてますか？
Are you ready?
とんでもないよ、声で揺れてるよ。
That's incredible, the floor is shaking from your voices.
はい、ということで、常闇トワ1stソロライブ、ここから始まりだー！
All right, then, Tokoyami Towa's 1st Solo Live starts now!
行くぞ、悪魔ー！
Let's go, devils!
斬新素敵なバイオレット
A novel and wonderful violet
尖って参上　悪魔的最強
Sharply arriving, the strongest devil
あなたの背中に闇を点け
Lighting up the darkness on your back
小悪魔だって恐ろしい
Even a little devil can be terrifying
勧善懲悪　随を呈そう
Let's present the essence of rewarding good and punishing evil
抗って最後　振り切って最強
Resisting until the end, breaking free to be the strongest
自堕落少女　鎖付き
A depraved girl with chains
あくまで秘密の種につき
Merely a secret seed
何千回を　爪を研いで
Sharpening claws thousands of times,
機を伺って
waiting for the chance
準備完了　これで誕生　永遠に尽くすだろう
Preparation complete, born here, I will serve forever
悪魔的回転で　掻き回して
Stirring things up with a devilish spin
常闇が舞いなら　撃ち落とす
If the eternal darkness dances, I'll shoot it down
Do-be do-be　太刀振る舞い
Do-be do-be, my behavior
Bi-bi bi-bi　奈落の底から
Bi-bi bi-bi, from the depths of hell
人間界　波乱万丈
The human world is full of ups and downs
常識がないなら　奪われる
If you have no common sense, you'll be robbed
Do-be do-be　悪魔の名
Do-be do-be, the name of a devil
影を撃って　Yeah
Shoot the shadow, yeah
斬新素敵なバイオレット
A novel and wonderful violet
切り込みハイに　溶け込んで倍に
Cutting into the back, merging and doubling
あなたの心に忍び込み
Slipping into your heart
小悪魔だって恐ろしい
Even a little devil can be terrifying
一網打尽　寄って集え
A clean sweep, gather together
ならば他誰　敵は誰
Then who else, who is the enemy?
面従腹背　旅　つける錆
Obeying in public but defying in private, a journey of rust
あれば君に
If so, to you...
Ready steady set!
悪魔と連弾　肺繋いで　相手にならないと喰らうほど
A duet with a devil, lungs connected, so much that you'll be eaten if you can't keep up
Debby Debby ガッツだ少年！ Vivi Vivi 世界はフィクション
Debby Debby, show some guts, boy! Vivi Vivi, the world is fiction
健全なモードなんて　今だけは全てを恨めばいい
As for a wholesome mode, just for now you should resent everything
Debby Debby 悪魔の輪　闇を知ってイェイ
Debby Debby, the devil's ring, knowing the darkness, yay
消えない寂しさとな　言えない傷跡を繋げ
Connect the loneliness that doesn't fade with the scars you can't talk about
歩みを止めないなんて　お利口な人間は
Not stopping their progress, those well-behaved humans
時代を宣告して死んじゃって　光を生み出した
Proclaimed the era and died, giving birth to the light
悪魔の所業で　お利口な人間　イェイ
With the devil's work, the well-behaved human, yay
悪魔と連弾　吐息吐いて　どこも光がないな　渦を巻く
A duet with a devil, breathing sighs, there's no light anywhere, swirling in a vortex
Debby Debby 懐かしい快鳴 Vivi Vivi 奈落の底から
Debby Debby, a nostalgic pleasant sound, Vivi Vivi, from the bottom of the abyss
人間界カードなんて　常識がないなら奪われる
As for the human world cards, if you have no common sense, they'll be stolen
Debby Debby 悪魔の輪　影を撃って
Debby Debby, the devil's ring, shoot the shadow
悪魔と連弾　肺繋いで　相手にならないと喰らうほど
A duet with a devil, lungs connected, so much that you'll be eaten if you can't keep up
Debby Debby ガッツだ少年！ Vivi Vivi 世界はフィクション
Debby Debby, show some guts, boy! Vivi Vivi, the world is fiction
健全なモードなんて　今だけは全てを恨めばいい
As for a wholesome mode, just for now you should resent everything
Debby Debby 悪魔の輪　闇を知ってイェイ
Debby Debby, the devil's ring, knowing the darkness, yay
ヘイ！ ヘイ！ ヘイ！ ヘイ！
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
まだまだもっと！声出していけるんじゃないのー！？
More, more! You can shout even louder, can't you!?
いくぞー！
Here we go!
だって私　いつまでも　ずっと虜
Because I'll always be captivated by you
君以外は　もうありえない
No one else is possible anymore
ちょっといつも　フラフラ　そっぽ向くの
Always a bit unsteady, looking away
思わせぶり　揺るがないなら
Suggestive, if you're unshakeable
好きだよって　微笑んで　誤魔化してもし
Even if I smile and say "I love you" to hide it
あのね　無理だよって　逃げるよって
You know, saying it's impossible, that you'll run away
ガラスハートを　振り回して　骨の髄まで　しゃぶりつくして
Swinging a glass heart around, sucking it to the marrow of the bone
壊れるほど　惑わせて　You know, You know, You know
Bewildering me enough to break me, You know, You know, You know
ラブストーリーを　転がして　時空金剛　駆け抜けて
Rolling the love story, running through space-time diamond
痺れる声を　雷鳴
A numbing voice, a thunderclap
無料パートは終了いたしました！
The free part has ended!
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
Thank you for watching!
無料パートは終了いたしました！
The free part has ended!
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
Thank you for watching!